Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Museum Guest Scholar and Conservator Files, 1978-2005 IA10013
Institutional Records and Archives
- Guest scholar and visiting conservator files, 1978-1996; Series I.; 5 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
  - Guest Scholar Files
    - Williams, Patterson B. – Education and Academic Affairs, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Wilson, Ms. Elizabeth – Sculpture, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Wilson, Michael – [Museum], 1995–1996? (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Wixom, Dr. William D – Manuscripts, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Wolbers, Richard – Conservation Departments, 1992–1993 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Yamagishi, Koko – Photographs, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Zafran, Eric M. – Paintings, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Zeck, Iouna – Decorative Arts, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Zeki, Semir – [?], 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
  - Visiting Conservator Files
    - Asmus, Dr. John – Antiquities, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Baas, Valerie – Photographs, 1992–1993 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Baas, Valerie – Photographs, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Baldini, Umberto – Paintings, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Ballard, Mary – Decorative Arts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Barcillon, Pinin B. – Paintings, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Beaudin, Jill Sterret – Photographs, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Bigolin, Antonio – Paintings, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Born, Hermann – Antiquities, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Bowen, Ms. Craigen W. – Drawings, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Brodrick, Anne – Decorative Arts, 1992–1993 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Burmeister, Andreas – Scientific, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Cadorin, Paolo – Paintings, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Cains, Anthony G. – Manuscripts, 1988–1989 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Cartier–Bresson, Anne – Photographs, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Casazza, Ornella – Paintings, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Chase, W.T. – Decorative Arts, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Clarkson, Christopher – Manuscripts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Clarkson, Christopher – Manuscripts, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Colalucci, Gianluigi – Paintings, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Colalucci, Gianluigi – Paintings, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - D'Alessandro, Ms. Lorenza M.G. – Antiquities, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - De Witte, Eddy – Antiquities, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Donnithorne, Alan Richard – Drawings, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Drilhon, France – Antiquities, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Evetts, Deborah – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Formigli, Edilberto – Antiquities, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Fuchs, Robert – Manuscripts, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Futernick, Robert – Drawings, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Goldrach, Alain – Paintings, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Grimm, Carl – Paintings, 1988–1989 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hacke, Bent – Paintings, 1986–1987 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hawkins, David – Decorative Arts, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hermanes, Theo–Antoine – Decorative Arts, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hiedelberg, Michael – Paintings, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hill, Dorothy Kent – Antiquities, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hlopoff, Rostislav – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hofenk–De Graaff, Judith – Decorative Arts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Hutchins, Jane – Decorative Arts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Ignatiadou, Despina – Antiquities, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Jessell, Bettina – Paintings, 1979–1980 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Kajitani, Nobuko – Decorative Arts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Keyes, Keiko M. – Drawings, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Keyes, Keiko Mizushima – Drawings, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Kopelman, Gabrielle – Paintings, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Koynova Arnaudova, Lozinka – Antiquities, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Kruger, Jerry – Decorative Arts, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Kushel, Dan – Antiquities, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Lahanier, Christian – Scientific, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Larson, John – Antiquities, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Lie, Henry – Antiquities, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Lins, P. Andrew – Decorative Arts, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Lins, P. Andrew – Decorative Arts, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Lunning, Elizabeth – Drawings, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - McElhone, John P. – Photographs, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mc Intyre, Ian – Antiquities, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Masschelein–Kleiner, Liliane – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mattusch, Carol – Antiquities, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Matteini, Mauro – Scientific, Conservation Institute, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mitchell, Paul – Paintings, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mora, Laura – Paintings, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mora, Paolo and Laura – Paintings, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Mora, Paolo – Antiquities, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Motta, Edson – Paintings, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Moor, Angela and Ian – Photographs, 1988–1989 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Muller, Norman E. – Paintings, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Musatti, Gianna – Antiquities, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Nardi, Roberto – Antiquities, 1992–1993 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Oddy, Andrew – Antiquities, 1986–1987 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Ogden, Jack – Antiquities, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Oltrogge, Doris – Manuscripts, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Pickwoad, Nicholas – Manuscripts, 1992–1993 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Perkinson, Roy – Drawings, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Petherbridge, Guy T. – Manuscripts, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Plesters, Joyce – Paintings, 1979–1980 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Preusser, Frank – Antiquities, 1980–1981 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Quandt, Ms. Abigail – Manuscripts, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Rabin, Bernard – Paintings, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Ramond, Pierre – Decorative Arts, 1991–1992 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Ramond, Pierre – Decorative Arts, 1984–1985 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Richter, Ernst – Scientific, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Roby, Mr. Thomas – Antiquities, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Rockwell, Peter – Decorative Arts, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Roy, Ashok – Paintings, 1987–1988 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Sallé, Jean – Decorative Arts, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Schleicher, Barbara – Paintings, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Seeley, Nigel – Antiquities, 1981–1982 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Serck–Dewaide, Myriam – Decorative Arts, 1990–1991 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Shelley, Marjorie – Drawings, 1988–1989 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Soultanian, Jack – Decorative Arts and Sculpture, 1995–1996 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Sramek, Jiri – Antiquities, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Stambolov, Todor – Antiquities, 1981–1982 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Stone, Richard – Decorative Arts, 1989–1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Stoner, Joyce Hill – Paintings, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Thornton, Mr. Jonathan – Decorative Arts, 1994–1995 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Torraca, Giorgio – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Van De Wetering, E. – Antiquities, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Von Sonnenburg, Hubert – Paintings, 1983–1984 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Wald, Robert – Paintings, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Waldeis, Peter – Paintings, 1993–1994 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Weintraub, Stephen – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Weisser, Terry – Antiquities, 1985–1986 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Werner, A.E. – Antiquities, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Wolbers, Richard – Paintings, 1986–1987 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
    - Wright, Charles – Decorative Arts, 1982–1983 (Box 2007.IA.07-05)
  - Administrative Files
    - Guest Scholars:
      - A Guide to the Library (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Center Access Form (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Emergency Information Form (Historical Use Only) (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Grant Evaluation (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Grant Evaluation Analysis/Nationalities (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - L.A. Orientation Brochure (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Museum Orientation Brochure (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Non–Guest Scholar Use of Cars Prior to Geo Prisms, August 1990 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Orientation Meetings Agenda (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Payroll Policy (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Shipping and Freight Information (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Shipping and Freight Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Special Events – Previous Years (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Consultation Information (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Consultation Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Interview Questionnaire (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Information (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Interview Questionnaire (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Policies (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Policy History (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Reference Materials (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Treatments of Grants Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Travel and Residency Information Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - UCLA Faculty Status Letter (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Personal Data Form (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Data Processing Policies (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Health Insurance Coverage Information (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Information on Arrival in Los Angeles (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Preliminary J–1 Visa Form (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Emergency Notification Information Form (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Project Form (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Social Security Information Questionnaire (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Tax Package Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Office Inventory Checklist (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
    - Visiting Conservators:
      - Checklist – Visiting Conservator (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Host Responsibility Memo (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Welcome Letter(s): 1 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Welcome Letter(s): 2 (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Welcome Letters – Previous Years (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Request for Missing Forms (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Slate – Visiting Conservator – Current (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Slate – Visiting Conservator – Previous Years (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Selection – Previous Years (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Nomination Forms (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Visiting Conservator Information/Meeting Current (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Nomination Letter – JW [John Walsh] (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Hotels: Guest Quarters Suite Hotel (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Contract Terms – Previous (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Contract Letter – Non–Resident (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
      - Contract Letter – Resident (Box 2007.IA.07-04)
- Guest scholar photographs, 1979-2005; Series II.; 2.25 Linear Feet (9 binders and 1 box)
  Arrangement
  These records are arranged in chronological order.
  Photograph albums documenting the activities of museum scholars while at the Getty Center, dating 1979–2005. Photograph albums contain largely informal snapshots of daily scholar life at the Getty, taken at luncheons, lectures, exhibition openings, scholar housing and offices as well as other social events. Albums consist mainly of photographic prints, but also contain some negatives and slides. The majority of all images are unlabeled.
  - Scholar years, 1979–1980, 1981-1982, 1982–1983 (Box 2006.IA.25–1)
  - Scholar years, 1983–1984, 1984–1985 (Box 2006.IA.25–2)
  - Scholar years, 1985–1986, 1986–1987 (Box 2006.IA.25–3)
  - Scholar years, 1987–1988, 1988–1989, 1989–1990 (Box 2006.IA.25–4)
  - Scholar years, 1990–1991, 1991–1992, 1992–1993; undated (Box 2006.IA.25–5)
  - 1998–2001 (Box 2006.IA.25–6)
  - 2001–2003 (Box 2006.IA.25–7)
  - 2004–2005 (Box 2006.IA.25–8)
  - Compilation of visiting scholars, interns, and lecturers, (dismantled photo album), 1979–1987 (Box 2006.IA.25–9)
  - Photocopy of the original compilation photo album, 1979–1987 (Box 2006.IA.25–10)